Galgal Channel GO!
Yes, this is Haruta To.
I've been announcing this for a while now,
I've practiced DJing for the first time,
I'm taking this picture because I wanted to show you guys what I've been doing.
I started from a place where I really knew nothing about DJing,
I think there are still a lot of things I need to work on,
I'm going to work even harder and try my best to be able to do live performances,
I would be very happy if you could see the first steps of the project.
Please take a look at the first stage of the video.
Just, just give me love!
♪ Just, just give me love!
♪ Oh, chew up my next!
I'm sure you'll miss me, too.
Wow wow wow wow wow
We'll just have to wait it out.
When I met you, I knew...
I'm not alone
The world is bigger than this
Because I can do it
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
I'm so excited
We all make mistakes at some point
But it's a chance
Let's just keep going and going and going
Let's go, if we're together we're not afraid
Chu appa ne
I love you, I love you, I love you
Hey! I love you, I love you, I can't help it
If you like me and I like you, I'll tell you, I'm thrilled and colorful
I love you, I love you, I love you, I can't help it
I love you, I love you, I love you
Hey! I love you, I love you, I can't help it
Hey! If you like me, like me, like me, I'll sing to you
I'll sing this love to you Forever
Just give me love
The story always begins
From believing in 1% of the future
But if it's with you, I might just take the plunge
I think it might work out I think it might work out
So come along with me
Three, two, one.
Go, go, go, go
Come on, come on, come on, I'm in love with you
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I can make up a new storyline. A happy storyline.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
We'll always be friends.
Come on, baby
With you, we'll get there
I'll reach my dream I'll make it come true Start
If you tie the stars that shine in so many colors
I want to know, I want to hear, I want to be
No matter how many times I cry, no matter how many times I give up
I believe in the future that will bloom in the fullness of the sky
Let's go, let's start on the seventh star
Start with you, I'm sure we'll get there
Start with your dreams, start with me, start with me
Start, even if you have to reach for it
Every time I saw you in class, you shined brighter than anyone else
I had a premonition when I saw you eye to eye
This sparkle that I saw in your eyes was a miracle
I didn't realize it was love
I'm so close, I'm 30 centimeters from you
It seemed to reach me, but I couldn't reach it
I'm so close to you, but I can't grab you
I still love you, but I can't say it today
I can't tell you how much I love you
I don't know if you'll even notice
I can't reach it
Let's go!
I can't stop listening to this Heartbeat
I can't wait to tell someone
Do a Do a Peace
Baby Woo Woo Woo
Put on your new sneakers
Let's reach for the blue sky
Do a Do a Peace
Beautiful
Diamonds sparkle
A smile more dazzling
It's not a hard word
Like a prism
Oh baby
Show you something that hits my heart
I've done something hot
Show you something that'll make my heart beat
I need your love
Show you I need your love
I've done something hot
I need your love
You and I Look at me, Smile
Look at me more, Smile
I need you baby
Lucky, lucky, lucky, secret party
Let's have more fun with the girlsLet's enjoy girls more!
Happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy, happy
Don't be shy, confide in me All right
Lately I've been a little down in the dumps
Making up a smile isn't pretty enough
Reality's easier than you think
I'm looking for a little more excitement, a little more passion, a little more excitement.
Let's get together and get dressed up
Let's get all dressed up Let's pack all our favorite things
Everybody Everybody, ready to go All right
♪ It's show time, I've got my cute make-up on
Let's go make him know what you're into
Hey! It's amazing time!
It's amazing time!
Lucky lucky lucky Secret party
Let's have more fun as a girl
Happy happy happy Happy happy, we can talk about our love lives
Don't be shy, don't be shy, don't be shy
Aura!
Let's hear the music, let's hear the music, let's hear the music, let's hear the music, let's hear the music
We've got to have fun
Story that lasts I'll see you tomorrow, won't I?
Because you're here
Let's go!
Oh Yeah!
Just for now, if you go far enough
Doki-Doki Doki no Rear Time You're Right!
You'll feel the tension But naturally
Let's go! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Tell me?
I've been thinking about you for hours So Endless
Oh Yeah!
After School Party Time
Don't make me see you
Slow down and relax with the usual you Step by Step All right
I'll fall in love with you Passion I'm sure you'll feel it Passion
Don't worry Hey
If you have the best smile Win Win Win
I know you know I'm in love I can't stop the excitement Skill Girls
Hey, Are you smiling?
My love, your love Common points of attraction that I feel every time we admit to each other
One, two, three Stick me close
Hey! It's okay, it's okay, it's okay It's like I fell under the spell of the word "okay
Don't worry, I can go anywhere
There's nothing to be afraid of anymore
Since we met on that day
Each one of them is a precious note
If we all play together, it's the best harmony
If I can't stop crying, alone
Even if you walk around with your face down and your tongue turned away
I'll cast a smile spell on you
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, if we're together
We can overcome any difficulty
Don't worry, the future is bright
Step by step, we'll go on
It's all right, it's all right I'll always be with you
I'm with you every step of the way
It's okay.
One small step at a time
It'll give you courage.
And one day, it'll turn into confidence
It will fill your heart
A spell to make you smile
For you too, echo around the world
To the song
I'll be fine, I'll be fine, I'll be fine, I'll be fine
It's like I'm under a spell
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay I can fly anywhere
If we're together, we'll be fine
Okay, thank you for listening. How was your first time as a DJ?
I was very nervous while I was filming. As I said at the beginning, I'll do my best so that one day I can go to a live performance and show you in person where you want to go.
Thank you very much for watching today.
If you like this video, please give it a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to our channel.